How to Play
Player swipes on the screen to move the fireball, then adjusts the force and direction of the ball.
The player shoots the fireball which falls into a Golden Cup to complete the level.
If the player shoots the fireball outside the Golden Cup, they will play that level again.
Before playing the game, the player should create a profile with a picture and nickname.
Start
遊び方
プレイヤーがスクリーン上でスワイプして火球を移動させ、ボールの力と方向を調整する。
プレイヤーはレベルを完了するためにゴールデンカップに落ちる火球を撃つ。
もしゴールデンカップの外で火球を撃ったら、プレイヤーは再びそのレベルをプレイする。
ゲームをプレイする前に、プレイヤーは写真とニックネームのあるプロフィールを作成する必要である。
スタート
游戏说明
玩家在屏幕上滑动移动火球，调整球的力量和方向。
玩家射击火球，若火球落入金杯中则完成一个等级。
如果玩家射出的火球落在金杯之外，则玩家需在同一等级继续进行游戏。
在玩游戏之前，玩家应该创建一个带有图片和昵称个人资料。
开始
遊戲說明
玩家在屏幕上滑動移動火球，調整球的力量和方向。
玩家射擊火球，若火球落入金杯中則完成一個等級
如果玩家射出的火球落在金杯之外，則玩家需在同一等級繼續進行遊戲。
在玩游戏之前，玩家应该创建一个带有图片和昵称个人资料。
開始
कैसे खेलें
फायर बॉल को स्थानांतरित करने के लिए खिलाड़ी स्क्रीन पर स्वाइप करता है, फिर गेंद के बल और दिशा को समायोजित करता है।
खिलाड़ी आग का गोला मारता है जो स्तर को पूरा करने के लिए एक सुनहरा कप में गिरता है।
अगर खिलाड़ी गोल्डन कप के बाहर आग का गोला गोली मारता है, तो वे उस स्तर पर फिर से खेलेंगे।

प्रारंभ
Como jugar
Jugador deslizar en la pantalla para mover la bola de fuego, ajustar la fuerza y la dirección de la bola.
El jugador dispara la bola de fuego que cae en una Copa de Oro para completar el nivel.
Si el jugador tira la bola de fuego de la Copa de Oro, el jugador jugará ese nivel otra vez.

Comienzo
Comment jouer
Jouer  doit  toucher l'écran pour déménager la balle de feu  en ajustant la force et l'orientation du balle.
Le joueur doit tirer la balle de feu tombé dans la Coupe d'Or pour passer ce niveau.
Si le joueur  a trompé, il faut jouer le même niveau  encore une fois.

Depart
게임 방법
플레이어가 화면을 스와이프하여 파이어볼을 움직이고, 힘조절과 방향 조절이 가능합니다.
플레이어는 황금 컵에 떨어지는 파이어볼을 쏘아서 레벨을 완료합니다.
플레이어가 황금 컵밖으로 파이어볼을 쏘면 플레이어는 다시 그 레벨을 플레이하게됩니다.
게임을하기 전에 플레이어는 사진과 닉네임이있는 프로파일을 만들어야합니다.
스타트
Hướng dẫn chơi
Người chơi sẽ chạm vào màn hình để di chuyển quả cầu lửa, sau đó điều chỉnh lực bắn và hướng bay của quả cầu.
Người chơi sẽ phải bắn quả cầu lửa rơi vào trong chiếc Cốc vàng để kết thúc Cấp độ đang chơi.
Nếu người chơi bắn quả cầu lửa rơi ra ngoài chiếc Cốc vàng, thì sẽ phải chơi lại Cấp độ đó lần nữa.
Trước khi chơi game, người chơi phải tạo hồ sơ cá nhân với ảnh và biệt danh.
Bắt đầu
